Robert Hupka Collection of Toscanini Test Pressings and Dom Baron Chant Recordings
Robert Hupka Collection of Toscanini Test Pressings
- Toscanini recordings
  - Carmen - Chanson du toréador (Toreador Song) - Bizet, [09/18]/1903; hupka_1976; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Chanson du toréador (Toreador Song) - Bizet, [04/18]/1905; hupka_1977; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Euvaiu pour eviter - Bizet, hupka_3430; Z-5493-F; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Final Duet - Bizet (Pt. 1), hupka_1145; Serial # CS-4261-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Final Duet - Bizet (Pt. 2), hupka_1126; Serial # CS-4262-3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Final Duet - Bizet (Pt. 2), hupka_1146; Serial # CS-4262-IT1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Final Scene, No, mai Carmen non cedarà - Bizet (Pt. 2), 3/12/1930; hupka_3782; 7314-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Final Scene, Sei tu? - Bizet (Pt. 1), 3/12/1930; hupka_3781; 7314-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Finale, Ebben, Carmen, io t'amo ancora - Bizet, circa 1919-1923; hupka_3791; 2F-386-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Flower Song - Bizet, [01/25/1905]; hupka_0887; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Flower Song - Bizet, 11/25/1912; hupka_1056; Serial # 85122; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Habanera - Bizet, 1903; hupka_1070; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Habanera - Bizet, 6/6/1905; hupka_3578; Cat # 64022; B-2605; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Habanera - Bizet, hupka_4015; Serial # 92059; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Habanera - Bizet, 12/9/1910; hupka_4024; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Il fior - Bizet, 1908; hupka_1228; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Il fior - Bizet, 1/7/1910; hupka_1279; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Il fior - Bizet, 2/27/1905; hupka_3657; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Il fior - Bizet, 1/31/1929; hupka_3780; 6961-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Je dis que rien ne m'épouvante (Micaela's air) - Bizet, 5/14/1906; hupka_1018; Serial # IRCC-32-B;88036; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Je suis Escamillo - Bizet, [02/19]/1907; hupka_1055; Serial # IRCC-169-A; Shellac disc
  - Carmen - Là-bas dans la montagne - Bizet, [03/20/1908]; hupka_1968; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - La tua madre - Bizet, 1903; hupka_1037; Serial # 92052; DB 359; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Le fior? - Bizet, 1903; hupka_1036; Serial # 92028; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Lo dico (Michaela's aria) - Gounod, 4/15/1911; hupka_1189; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Nôtre méteir est bon (Sextet) - Bizet, 3/25/1910; hupka_3822; B-8745; Unpublished; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Nous avons en tête - Bizet, 3/25/1910; hupka_1177; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Parle moi de ma mere - Bizet, 1/14/1924; hupka_1960; HRS-1039-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Seguidilla - Bizet, hupka_1496; Serial # 1285-R; Cat # IRCC-122-B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Carmen - Si tu m'ami - Bizet, 3/22/1912; hupka_1108; Shellac disc
  - Carmen - Toreador Song - Bizet, [10/04/1922]; hupka_1050; Shellac disc
  - Caro mio ben - Umberto Giordano, hupka_1106; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria Rusticana - Abschied von der Mutter - Pietro Mascagni, Jun. 1907; hupka_3068; Serial # 10850-U; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria Rusticana - Addio alla madre - Pietro Mascagni, circa 1906-1917; hupka_1947; 2SB-2403-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria Rusticana - Addio alla Madre - Pietro Mascagni, circa 1937-1949; hupka_1935; 2SB-2403-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria Rusticana - Addio alla Madre - Pietro Mascagni, circa 1937-1949; hupka_1936; 2SB-2403-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria Rusticana - Addio alla madre - Pietro Mascagni, 12/8/1910; hupka_1243; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria Rusticana - Brindisi - Pietro Mascagni, 10/7/1909; hupka_2071; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria Rusticana - Brindisi [Beviamone un bicchiere...Viva il vino] - Pietro Mascagni, 2/9/1905; hupka_2788; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria Rusticana - O Lola (Siciliana) - Pietro Mascagni, [1907]; hupka_3046; Serial # 10858-U; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria Rusticana - Siciliana - Pietro Mascagni, 1902; hupka_1958; "Very valuable"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria Rusticana - Siciliana - Pietro Mascagni, 1902; hupka_1970; "Very valuable"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria Rusticana - Siciliana - Pietro Mascagni, 1902; hupka_2457; "Very valuable"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria Rusticana - Siciliana - Pietro Mascagni, [02/27]/1905; hupka_2469; Serial # A 2344; Cat # 81062; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria rusticana - Voi lo sapete - Pietro Mascagni, [05/14/1906]; hupka_0994; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria Rusticana - Voi lo sapete - Pietro Mascagni, 1908; hupka_1952; 1420½C; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cavalleria Rusticana - Voi lo sapete, o Mamma - Pietro Mascagni, [7/27]/1906; hupka_2000; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Céphale et Procris - Elisabeth Jacquet de la Guerre (Part 1), hupka_1368; D5-RC-366-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Charité - Fauré, 1/9/1912; hupka_1222; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Choral Fantasy for Piano, Chorus, and Orchestra in C Major, op. 80 - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 12/2/1939; hupka_1431; "Not listed"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Choral Fantasy for Piano, Chorus, and Orchestra in C Major, op. 80 - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 12/2/1939; hupka_1432; "Not listed"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Choral Fantasy for Piano, Chorus, and Orchestra in C Major, op. 80 - Beethoven (Pt. 3), 12/2/1939; hupka_1433; "Not listed"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Choral Fantasy for Piano, Chorus, and Orchestra in C Major, op. 80 - Beethoven (Pt. 4), 12/2/1939; hupka_1434; "Not listed"; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Choral Fantasy in C Major for Piano, Chorus & Orchestra, op. 80 - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 12/2/1939; hupka_2262; Shellac disc
  - Choral Fantasy in C Major for Piano, Chorus & Orchestra, op. 80 - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 12/2/1939; hupka_2265; Shellac disc
  - Choral Fantasy in C Major for Piano, Chorus & Orchestra, op. 80 - Beethoven (Pt. 3), 12/2/1939; hupka_2266; Shellac disc
  - Choral Fantasy in C Major for Piano, Chorus & Orchestra, op. 80 - Beethoven (Pt. 4), 12/2/1939; hupka_2267; Shellac disc
  - Choral Fantasy in C Major, op. 80 - Part 1 - Beethoven, 12/2/1939; hupka_1654; Record # 045600-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Choral Fantasy in C Major, op. 80 - Part 2 - Beethoven, 12/2/1939; hupka_1776; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Choral Fantasy in C Major, op. 80 - Part 3 - Beethoven, 12/2/1939; hupka_1898; Record # 045602-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Choral Fantasy in C Major, op. 80 - Part 4 - Beethoven, 12/2/1939; hupka_2018; Record # 045603-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Choral Fantasy in C minor, op. 80 - Beethoven, 12/2/1939; hupka_3143; Sides 2 & 4; Benefit concert for NY Junior League Welfare Fund; Shellac disc
  - Choral Fantasy in C minor, op. 80, Symphony No. 9 in D minor (Choral), op. 125 - Beethoven, 12/2/1939; hupka_3140; Sides 2 & 4; Benefit concert for NY Junior League Welfare Fund; Shellac disc
  - Choral Fantasy, op. 80 - Beethoven, hupka_0111; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Choral Fantasy, op. 80 - Beethoven, 12/2/1939; hupka_0669; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Choral Fantasy, op. 80 [?], Missa Solemnis, op. 123 - Kyrie - Beethoven, hupka_0115; Includes a note to producer Peter Munves from Toscanini dated 02/04/72, saying: "Since we both orbit in crazy circles, and getting together is difficult, here is something to hold you over"; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Choral Fantasy, op. 80 and Missa Solemnis - Kyrie - Beethoven, 12/2/1939; 12/28/1940; hupka_0665; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Choral Fantasy, op. 80, Missa Solemnis, op. 123 - Kyrie - Beethoven, 12/2/1939; 12/28/1940; hupka_0164; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Choral Fantasy, op. 80, Symphony No. 5 in C minor, op. 67, Missa Solemnis, op. 123 - Kyrie - Beethoven, May 1933; 12/02/1939; 12/28/1940; hupka_0106; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Christmas Carols, Dec. 1954; hupka_4153; Sides 1 & 2; F8-OP-0870 & 0871; VinylDisc
  - Christmas Concert, 1956; hupka_3236; VinylDisc
  - Classical Symphony - Prokofiev (Part 1), 6/25/1944; hupka_1323; 481-A; D5-TC-255-1; Shellac disc
  - Classical Symphony - Prokofiev (Part 2), 6/25/1944; hupka_1324; 481-B; D5-TC-256-1; Shellac disc
  - Colas Breugnon - Overture - Kabalevsky, hupka_3320; D6-RC-5276-2A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Colas Breugnon - Overture - Kabalevsky; The Spider's Feast - Roussel; Sarabande - Jean Roger-Ducasse; Romeo and Juliet - Tchaikovsky, 4/6/1946; hupka_2661; Rehearsal [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04/06/1946 rehearsal - it is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Sides 1 & 3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Colas Breugnon - Overture - Kabalevsky; The Spider's Feast - Roussel; Sarabande - Jean Roger-Ducasse; Romeo and Juliet - Tchaikovsky, 4/6/1946; hupka_2662; Rehearsal [Note - Pieces listed under "title" are from the 04/06/1946 rehearsal - it is unknown which tracks are on this item]; Side 2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Come my Beloved - Handel, 6/2/1924; hupka_3761; IRCC-60-A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Come un bel di maggio - Andrea Chenier, circa 1937-1940s; hupka_1338; Serial # OSB-2397-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Come un bel di maggio - Andrea Chenier, circa 1937-1940s; hupka_1350; Serial # OSB-2397-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Come un bel di maggio - Andrea Chenier, circa 1937-1940s; hupka_1362; Serial # OSB-2397-2; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Comparison of Halls: Symphony No. 7 in A Major, op. 92 - Mvt. IV, Consecration of the House [Die Weihe des Hauses] - Beethoven, 3/16/1947; 10/25/1947; 11/19/1944; hupka_3150; Shellac disc
  - Concerto for Violin, Cello, Piano and Orchestra, op. 56 - Beethoven; Death and Transfiguration, op. 24 - R. Strauss, 5/1/1942; hupka_0187; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Concerto for Violin, Cello, Piano, and Orchestra in C Major, op. 56, [Choral] Fantasy, op. 80, Violin Concerto in D Major, op. 61 - Beethoven, hupka_0469; 1/4 inch audio tape
  - Concerto Grosso ? - Gavotte, Allegro - Handel, hupka_1913; D6-RC-5352-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concerto Grosso in B minor, op. 6, No. 12 - Mvt. I - Handel, 11/22/1947; hupka_2155; Record # D8-RC-656-1; Shellac disc
  - Concerto Grosso in B minor, op. 6, No. 12 - Mvt. I - Handel, 11/22/1947; hupka_3380; D8-RC-656-1; Shellac disc
  - Concerto Grosso in B minor, op. 6, No. 12 - Mvt. II - Handel, 11/22/1947; hupka_3381; D8-RC-657-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concerto Grosso in B minor, op. 6, No. 12 - Mvt. III & IV - Handel, 11/22/1947; hupka_3384; D8-RC-658-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concerto in B flat for Violin & String Orchestra - Mvt. I - Vivaldi (Part 1), 11/22/1947; hupka_2094; Record # D8-RC-647-1; Shellac disc
  - Concerto in B flat for Violin & String Orchestra - Mvt. I - Vivaldi (Part 1), 11/22/1947; hupka_2237; Record # D8-RC-648-1A; Shellac disc
  - Concerto in B flat for Violin & String Orchestra - Mvt. II - Vivaldi, 11/22/1947; hupka_2225; Record # D8-RC-649-1; Shellac disc
  - Concerto in B flat for Violin & String Orchestra - Mvt. III - Vivaldi, 11/22/1947; hupka_2213; Record # D8-RC-650-1; Shellac disc
  - Concerto in B flat for Violin and Orchestra - Mvt. I - Vivaldi (Pt. 1), 11/22/1947; hupka_3370; D8-RC-647-1; Shellac disc
  - Concerto in B flat for Violin and Orchestra - Mvt. I - Vivaldi (Pt. 2), 11/22/1947; hupka_3372; D8-RC-648-1A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concerto in B flat for Violin and Orchestra - Mvt. II - Vivaldi (Pt. 1), 11/22/1947; hupka_3373; D8-RC-649-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concerto in B flat for Violin and Orchestra - Mvt. III - Vivaldi (Pt. 1), 11/22/1947; hupka_3374; D8-RC-650-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. I - Mendelssohn, broadcasted 4/9/1944; hupka_3882; Part 1; Record # D4-RC-137; Shellac disc
  - Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. I - Mendelssohn, Broadcasted 04/09/1944; hupka_4004; Part 2; Record # D4-RC-138; Shellac disc
  - Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. I & II - Mendelssohn, Broadcasted 04/09/1944; hupka_4126; Part 3; Record # D4-RC-139; Shellac disc
  - Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. II - Mendelssohn Part 4, 4/09/1944 (broadcast date); hupka_0922; Shellac disc
  - Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. III - Mendelssohn - Part 5, broadcasted 4/9/1944; hupka_1044; Shellac disc
  - Concerto in E minor, op. 64 - Mvt. III - Mendelssohn Part 6, broadcast 4/9/1944; hupka_1166; Shellac disc
  - Concerto No. 1 in B-flat minor, op. 23 - Mvt. II - Tschaikowsky (Part 2), 5/6/1941; hupka_1335; Shellac disc
  - Concerto No. 1 in B-flat minor, op. 23 - Mvt. II - Tschaikowsky (Part 2), hupka_1336; Shellac disc
  - Concierto No. 1 Para Piano y Orquestra [Piano Concerto No. 1 in C Major, op. 15] - Beethoven, hupka_2581; Record # ND5-MM-4205 & 4207; Mx # 62B & 63B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concierto No. 1 Para Piano y Orquestra [Piano Concerto No. 1 in C Major, op. 15] - Mvt. I, III; Cuarteto de Cuerdas, [String Quartet No. 16 in F Major], op. 135 - Lento assai; Egmont - Overture - Beethoven, hupka_2602; Record # ND5-MM-4204 & 4205 Mx # 62A & 62B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concierto No. 1 Para Piano y Orquestra [Piano Concerto No. 1 in C Major, op. 15] - Mvt. I, III; Cuarteto de Cuerdas, [String Quartet No. 16 in F Major], op. 135 - Vivace - Beethoven, hupka_2601; Record # ND5-MM-4206 & 4207 Mx # 63A & 63B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concierto No. 1 Para Piano y Orquestra [Piano Concerto No. 1 in C Major, op. 15]; Egmont - Overture; Cuarteto de Cuerdas, [String Quartet No. 16 in F Major] op. 135 - Lento assai, Vivace - Beethoven, hupka_2582; Record # ND5-MM-4204 & 4206; Mx # 62A & 63A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concierto No. 3 Para Piano y Orquestra [Piano Concerto No. 3 in C minor, op. 37] - Beethoven, hupka_2553; Record # ND5-MM-4342 & 4344; Mx # 68A & 69A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concierto No. 3 Para Piano y Orquestra [Piano Concerto No. 3 in C minor, op. 37] - Beethoven, hupka_2574; Record # ND5-MM-4342 & 4344; Mx # 68A & 69A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concierto No. 3 Para Piano y Orquestra [Piano Concerto No. 3 in C minor, op. 37] - Beethoven, hupka_2586; Record # ND5-MM-4342 & 4344; Mx # 68A & 69A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concierto No. 4 Para Piano y Orquestra [Pinao Concerto No. 4 in G Major, op. 58] - Beethoven, hupka_2562; Record # ND5-MM-4412 & 4410 Mx # 75B & 74B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concierto No. 4 Para Piano y Orquestra [Pinao Concerto No. 4 in G Major, op. 58] - Beethoven, hupka_2571; Record # ND5-MM-4412 & 4410; Mx # 75B & 74B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Concierto No. 4 Para Piano y Orquestra [Pinao Concerto No. 4 in G Major, op. 58] - Beethoven, hupka_2595; Record # ND5-MM-4412 & 4410; Mx # 75B & 74B; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Consecration of the House - Overture - Beethoven (Pt. 1), 3/16/1949; hupka_3288; D7-RC-8230-3; 12-0757-B; H 3/14; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Consecration of the House - Overture - Beethoven (Pt. 2), 3/16/1949; hupka_3290; D7-RC-8232-2; 12-0758-A; H 3/14; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Consecration of the House - Overture - Beethoven (Pt. 3), 3/16/1949; hupka_3292; D7-RC-8232-2; 12-0758-B; H 3/14; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Consecration of the House - Overture; The Creatures of Prometheus - Adagio and Allegretto - Beethoven, 3/19/1949; hupka_2640; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Consecration of the House, op. 124 - Overture; The Creatures of Prometheus, op. 43 - Adagio & Allegro; Symphony No. 6 in F Major, op. 68 - Beethoven, 3/14/1947; hupka_2781; Probably a rehearsal - record does not contain all of these pieces, but the tracks are taken from the list of the 03/16/47 broadcast; Sides 1 & 3; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Consecration of the House, op. 124 - Overture; The Creatures of Prometheus, op. 43 - Adagio & Allegro; Symphony No. 6 in F Major, op. 68 - Beethoven, 3/14/1947; hupka_2782; Probably a rehearsal - record does not contain all of these pieces, but the tracks are taken from the list of the 03/16/47 broadcast; Sides 2 & 4; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Consecration of the House, op. 124 - Overture; The Creatures of Prometheus, op. 43 - Adagio & Allegro; Symphony No. 6 in F Major, op. 68 - Beethoven, 3/14/1947; hupka_2783; Probably a rehearsal - record does not contain all of these pieces, but the tracks are taken from the list of the 03/16/47 broadcast; Sides 5 & 7; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Consecration of the House, op. 124 - Overture; The Creatures of Prometheus, op. 43 - Adagio & Allegro; Symphony No. 6 in F Major, op. 68 - Beethoven, 3/14/1947; hupka_2784; Probably a rehearsal - record does not contain all of these pieces, but the tracks are taken from the list of the 03/16/47 broadcast; Sides 6 & 8; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Consecration of the House, op. 124 - Overture; The Creatures of Prometheus, op. 43 - Adagio & Allegro; Symphony No. 6 in F Major, op. 68 - Beethoven, 3/14/1947; hupka_2785; Probably a rehearsal - record does not contain all of these pieces, but the tracks are taken from the list of the 03/16/47 broadcast; Side 9; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Consecration of the House, op. 124 - Overture; The Creatures of Prometheus, op. 43 - Adagio & Allegro; Symphony No. 6 in F Major, op. 68 - Beethoven, 3/14/1947; hupka_2786; Probably a rehearsal - record does not contain all of these pieces, but the tracks are taken from the list of the 03/16/47 broadcast; Side 10; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Consecration of the House, op. 124 - Overture; The Creatures of Prometheus, op. 43 - Adagio & Allegro; Symphony No. 6 in F Major, op. 68 - Beethoven, 3/15/1947; hupka_2803; Side 1; Probably a rehearsal - record does not contain all of these pieces, but tracks are taken from the list of the 03/16/47 broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Consecration of the House, op. 124 - Overture; The Creatures of Prometheus, op. 43 - Adagio & Allegro; Symphony No. 6 in F Major, op. 68 - Beethoven, 3/15/1947; hupka_2804; Sides 2 & 4; Probably a rehearsal - record does not contain all of these pieces, but tracks are taken from the list of the 03/16/47 broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Contest (Parts 1 & 3), hupka_2118; T-2737-1A; Shellac disc
  - The Contest (Parts 2 & 4), hupka_2132; T-2738-1; Shellac disc
  - Core'ngrato - ? Cardillo, hupka_3864; 012 840-1; unpublished; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Coriolan Overture - Beethoven (Part 1), hupka_2017; Record # D5-RC-488-2A; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture - Beethoven (Part 2), hupka_2030; Record # D5-RC-489-2; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_2195; Rehearsal - Studio 8-H; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_2196; Rehearsal - Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_2269; Rehearsal - Studio 8-H; Master; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_2270; Rehearsal - Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_2274; Rehearsal - Studio 8-H; Master; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_2277; Rehearsal - Studio 8-H; Master; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_2278; Rehearsal - Studio 8-H; Master; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_2279; Rehearsal - Studio 8-H; Master; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3015; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3017; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3019; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3021; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3025; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3027; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3029; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3031; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3033; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3073; Rehearsal; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3083; Rehearsal; Studio 8-H; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3084; Shellac disc
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3203; Rehearsal; QC-1614-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3210; Master (2); Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3221; Rehearsal; QC-1614-1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Coriolan Overture, op. 62 - Beethoven, 11/21/1946; hupka_3222; Rehearsal; QC-1614-1; Master # 1; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Coriolano Obertura, [Coriolan Overture] op. 62, Cavatina del Curarteto en Si bemol, [String Quartet No. 13 in B flat Major] op. 130, Excertos del Cuarteto en Do Meyor [String Quartet No. 9 in C Major, op. 59, No. 3] - Beethoven, hupka_2561; Record # ND5-MM-4409 & 4411 Mx # 74A & 75A; "Cuarteto" spelled wrong on side 74A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Coriolano Obertura, [Coriolan Overture] op. 62, Cavatina del Curarteto en Si bemol, [String Quartet No. 13 in B flat Major] op. 130, Excertos del Cuarteto en Do Meyor [String Quartet No. 9 in C Major, op. 59, No. 3] - Beethoven, hupka_2570; Record # ND5-MM-4409 & 4411 Mx # 74A & 75A; "Cuarteto" spelled wrong on side 74A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Coriolano Obertura, [Coriolan Overture] op. 62, Cavatina del Curarteto en Si bemol, [String Quartet No. 13 in B flat Major] op. 130, Excertos del Cuarteto en Do Meyor [String Quartet No. 9 in C Major, op. 59, No. 3] - Beethoven, hupka_2594; Record # ND5-MM-4409 & 4411 Mx # 74A & 75A; "Cuarteto" spelled wrong on side 74A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Corolian Overture - Beethoven; Octet - Scherzo - Mendelssohn; Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven, 6/1/1945; hupka_2738; Rehearsal [for recording session at Studio 8H; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [The Creatures of Prometheus] - Overture, Adagio and Allegretto - Beethoven; Sinfonia No. 6 [Symphony No. 6 in F Major, op. 68] - Mvt. I - Beethoven, hupka_2557; Record # ND5-MM-4346 & 4348; Mx # 70A & 71A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [The Creatures of Prometheus] - Overture, Adagio and Allegretto - Beethoven; Sinfonia No. 6 [Symphony No. 6 in F Major, op. 68] - Mvt. I - Beethoven, hupka_2564; Record # ND5-MM-4346 & 4348; Mx # 70A & 71A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - [The Creatures of Prometheus] - Overture, Adagio and Allegretto - Beethoven; Sinfonia No. 6 [Symphony No. 6 in F Major, op. 68] - Mvt. I - Beethoven, hupka_2588; Record # ND5-MM-4346 & 4348; Mx # 70A & 71A; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Creatures of Prometheus - Overture - Beethoven, 12/19/1944; hupka_3591; D4-RC-564-1; Recording session at studio 8-H; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - The Creatures of Prometheus - Overture; Symphony No. 4 in B flat Major, op. 60; Leonore - Overture No. 3 - Beethoven, 2/3/1951; hupka_2179; E1-LCC-3655 & 3656; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Credo d'amour - Édouard Trémisot, [1/22/1917]; hupka_3640; B 19113; Shellac disc
  - Crispino e la comare - Io non sono pìn l'Aunetta - Luigi Ricci & Federico Ricci, circa 1903-1915; hupka_3937; HO-520-AF; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cristoforo Columbo - Aman lassù le stelle - Alberto Franchetti, hupka_0846; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cristoforo Columbo - Aman lassù le stelle - Alberto Franchetti, 2/26/1914; hupka_0847; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Cristoforo Columbo - Dunque ho sognato - Alberto Franchetti, 4/14/1921; hupka_0848; Serial # A 25213; Lacquer discs/acetates
  - Crucifix - Fauré, 1911; hupka_3660; A-11442; Lacquer discs/acetates